{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_B._Redman",
    "predicate": "property/type",
    "object": "coach",
    "human_readable": "Robert B. Redman is a coach.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882299900054932,
            "question": "Is Robert B. Redman a coach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9338364601135254,
            "question": "Give an example of what a coach like Robert B. Redman might do."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8874249458312988,
            "question": "What are the responsibilities of a coach such as Robert B. Redman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8863220810890198,
            "question": "Who is Robert B. Redman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8327184319496155,
            "question": "What is Robert B. Redman's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7832961082458496,
            "question": "Describe Robert B. Redman's occupation."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7062135934829712,
            "question": "What role does Robert B. Redman have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6240095496177673,
            "question": "What field is Robert B. Redman involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5931808948516846,
            "question": "What type of work does Robert B. Redman do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4577476680278778,
            "question": "What does Robert B. Redman do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert B. Redman is a coach.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1399_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work does Robert B. Redman do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1399_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Robert B. Redman involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1399_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role does Robert B. Redman have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1399_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1399_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Robert B. Redman, including his roles as a football coach at Bloomsburg University and East Orange High School, and his achievements in coaching. Therefore, the triple \"Robert B. Redman is a coach\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Robert B. Redman's career as both a football player and a coach, including his roles at Bloomsburg University of Pennsylvania and East Orange High School. Therefore, the statement that he is a coach is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}